Guide to the Montana Attorney General's Office Records 1893-1969
Montana Historical Society Archives
- Dockets (correspondence and other material re cases)
  - Docket #5, case #295: Montana vs. Clinton Peck (rustling in Fergus County), 1928 (Box-folder 99 / 74)
  - Docket #5, case #296: Montana vs. Robert Keithley (re receipt of stolen cattle in Wolf Point), 1928 (Box-folder 99 / 75)
  - Docket #5, case #301: Montana vs. Barney McGreevey (re arson in Anaconda), 1928 (Box-folder 99 / 76)
  - Docket #5, case #302: Montana vs. J.G. Hodge (re carrying dangerous weapon with intent to commit assault in Deer Lodge), 1928 (Box-folder 99 / 77)
  - Docket #5, case #304: Carbon County vs. Charles H. Draper (to recover payment), 1928 (Box-folder 99 / 78)
  - Docket #5, case #307: Montana vs. John Konon (re assault in Fallon County), 1928-1929 (Box-folder 99 / 79)
  - Docket #5, case #312: Montana vs. Arthur Clay (re assault in Powder River County), 1928-1929 (Box-folder 99 / 80)
  - Docket #5, case #318: Montana vs. James Dailey and H.M. Hallin (re murder of Matthew Kokho at Warm Springs Hospital), 1927-1928 (Box-folder 99 / 81)
  - Docket #5, case #320: Minnesota, Saint Paul and Sault Sainte Marie Railway vs. Stewart et al., 1929 (Box-folder 99 / 82)
  - Docket #5, case #321: Montana for Workmens Compensation Fund vs. Gladstone Mines and Reduction Company, 1928-1930 (Box-folder 99 / 83)
  - Docket #5, case #324: Harriet E. Wilson vs. State Board of Land Commissioners (to quiet title on Daniels County land), 1928 (Box-folder 99 / 84)
  - Docket #5, case #327: Montana Fish and Game Commission vs. Fred Bowen (re collection of license fees), 1927-1928 (Box-folder 99 / 85)
  - Docket #5, case #329: W.H. Byrne vs. Fulton Oil Company (re constitutionality of royalty on mineral land), 1929 (Box-folder 99 / 86)
  - Docket #5, case #330: Montana ex rel. Samuel C. Hood vs. District Court of Silver Bow County (re morphine possession), 1929 (Box-folder 99 / 87)
  - Docket #5, case #332: Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul and Pacific Railway vs. W.E. Harmon, Treasurer of Montana (re taxation), 1929-1930 (Box-folder 99 / 88)
  - Docket #5, case #333: Montana vs. rose Mary Courchere et al. (re highway condemnation on Fort Peck Reservation), 1929 (Box-folder 99 / 89)
  - Docket #5, case #336: Buffalo Rapids Irrigation District vs. Anna Colleran et al. (to quiet title), 1929 (Box-folder 99 / 90)
  - Docket #5, case #338: Montana vs. Frank Gustin (re horse theft in Malta), 1929 (Box-folder 99 / 91)
  - Docket #5, case #340: Montana vs. J.A. Riley et al. (re right of way on highway at Bridge), 1929 (Box-folder 99 / 92)
  - Docket #5, case #341: First National Bank of Plains vs. Sanders County (re taxation), 1928-1929 (Box-folder 99 / 93)
  - Docket #5, case #342: Montana vs. Frank Gunn (re murder in Toole County), 1929-1930 (Box-folder 99 / 94)
  - Docket #5, case #346: Sheridan County vs. National Surety Company (re collection of insurance in robbery case), 1929 (Box-folder 99 / 95)
  - Docket #5, case #347: Montana vs. Dave C. Yegan (re rustling in Glacier County), 1929 (Box-folder 99 / 96)
  - Docket #5, case #348: Montana ex rel. Public Service Commission vs. Melvin A. Brannon, Chancellor of University (re state chemist's duty to analyze gasoline), 1927-1929 (Box-folder 99 / 97)
  - Docket #5, case #357: Montana vs. Timothy Nelson (re disbarment), 1929 (Box-folder 99 / 98)
  - Docket #5, case #357: Montana vs. J.C. Kinney (re Wibaux grazing lease), 1929-1935 (Box-folder 99 / 99)
  - Docket #5, case #366: Montana vs. John McDonnell (re collection of gasoline dealers' tax), 1929-1930 (Box-folder 99 / 100)
  - Docket #5, case #372: Montana vs. George W. Hall (re assault in Miles City), 1929-1930 (Box-folder 99 / 101)
  - Docket #5, case #374: Montana vs. Hibbing-Sunburst Oil Company (re petroleum license tax), 1930-1932 (Box-folder 99 / 102)
  - Docket #5, case #376: Montana vs. John C. Van Etten (re gasoline tax), 1930 (Box-folder 99 / 103)
  - Docket #5, case #379: Montana vs. Nat C. Lyford (re rustling in Missoula County), 1930 (Box-folder 99 / 104)
  - Docket #5, case #380: Thomas Henderson vs. Dawson County Commissioners (re school bonds), 1930 (Box-folder 99 / 105)
  - Docket #5, case #381: Montana vs. Ellis Clark (re liquor to minor in Havre), 1930 (Box-folder 99 / 106)
  - Docket #5, case #383: Montana vs. Harry Olson (re robbery in Powell County), 1930 (Box-folder 99 / 107)
  - Docket #5, case #386: Montana vs. Jess Starkweather (re burglary in Musselshell County; also contains material on political situation in county), 1930 (Box-folder 99 / 108)
  - Docket #5, case #390: Montana vs. Johnson Hall (re perjury in Billideaux murder trial in Glacier County), 1930 (Box-folder 99 / 109)
  - Docket #5, case #397: Dept. of Agriculture vs. O.L. DeVore, Gallatin County Sheriff (re recovery of value of property), 1930-1931 (Box-folder 99 / 110)
  - Docket #5, case #407: Montana vs. S.R. "Nig" Collins and Frank J. Fishback (re attempted rape and providing liquor to minors in Plentywood), 1930 (Box-folder 99 / 111)
  - Docket #5, case #408: Montana vs. William E. Letterman (re grand larceny by means of manipulation of stock in Madison County company), 1930 (Box-folder 99 / 112)
  - Docket #5, case #413: Montana vs. Yale Oil Corporation of South Dakota (re gas tax, see #535 for appeal), 1930 (Box-folder 99 / 113)
  - Docket #5, case #415, 416, 420: Montana vs. Delbert Rhoads, Thomas Horsford, and Rufus Morris, McCone County Commissioners; Homer A. Hoover vs. Thomas Horsford, McCone County Attorney; McCone County vs. Thomas Horsford, et al. (re malfeasance in office in construction of Wolf Point to Circle road), 1929-1930 (Box-folder 99 / 114)
  - Docket #5, case #422, 423: Montana vs. Mah Sam Hing; Montana vs. Hum Quock (re narcotics possession by Chinese men in Butte), 1930 (Box-folder 99 / 115)
  - Docket #5, case #424: Judith Basin county vs. John Livingston et al., Judith Basin County Commissioners (re cancellation of Dwyer contract for auditing), 1930 (Box-folder 99 / 116)
  - Docket #5, case #433: Bank of Miles City vs. Custer County (re taxes paid under protest), 1930-1931 (Box-folder 99 / 117)
  - Docket #5, case #436: Ray Lyman Wilbur, Secretary of Interior vs. United States of America, ex rel Ethel McLennar (re cancellation of oil and gas permits), 1930-1931 (Box-folder 99 / 118)
  - Docket #5, case #437: Montana ex rel. L.A. Foot vs. Alvin L. Hughes (re disbarment), 1930-1932 (Box-folder 99 / 119)
  - Docket #5, case #447: Glacier County vs. Ruth Hall Schlinskii and Boris A.S. Aronow (re title to Glacier County land), 1930-1931 (Box-folder 99 / 120)
  - Docket #5, case #450: R. Cook vs. Alfred Klein, Deputy State Fire Marshal (re condemnation of building in Cut Bank), 1930-1931 (Box-folder 99 / 121)
  - Docket #5, case #462, 463: Montana vs. S.B. Fairbanks; Montana vs. A.A. Freseman, Jr. (re Fergus County grain theft involving Judith Milling Company and Basin Elevator Company), 1930-1931 (Box-folder 99 / 122)
  - Docket #5, case #464: Montana vs. Alva Askin, Wesley Striker, and Bon Askin (re manslaughter in Ekalaka; see also #533 for appeal), 1930-1931 (Box-folder 99 / 123)
  - Docket #5, case #465: Montana vs. Michael Davis Lavelle (re murder in Flathead County), 1930 (Box-folder 99 / 124)
  - Docket #5, case #466, 467: Montana vs. Dogy Duncan (re murder and assault in Flathead County), 1930-1931 (Box-folder 99 / 125)
  - Docket #5, case #470: Paul Mancronell vs. Gullieck Syvertson et al (re delivery of grain in Conrad), 1930-1931 (Box-folder 99 / 125)
  - Docket #5, case #473: Montana vs. Eclipse Petroleum Company (re license tax), 1930-1931 (Box-folder 99 / 126)
  - Docket #5, case #475: Montana vs. Lionel C. Walsh and James F. Walsh (re Walsh Grain Company grain theft at Maudlow), 1930-1935 (Box-folder 99 / 127)
  - Docket #5, case #476: Montana vs. Bert LeDuc (re murder in Butte), 1930 (Box-folder 99 / 128)
  - Docket #5, case #480: Montana vs. Morris Ludwick (re arson in Missoula), 1931 (Box-folder 99 / 129)
  - Docket #5, case #485: Henry S. Wyman vs. Granite County Treasurer (re taxes paid under protest), 1931 (Box-folder 99 / 130)
  - Docket #5, case #492, 493: Montana vs. Carey Fine (re murder in Flathead County), 1931 (Box-folder 99 / 131)
  - Docket #5, case #494: Montana vs. Ira L. Triplett (re coal license tax), 1931 (Box-folder 99 / 132)
  - Docket #5, case #496, 532: Musselshell County vs. Morris Development Company (re taxation), 1931-1932 (Box-folder 99 / 133)
  - Docket #5, case #499: A.H. Stafford, Commissioner of Agriculture vs. Wilford Johnson, trustee for Judith Milling Company and Basin Elevator Company (re insolvency), 1930 (Box-folder 99 / 134)
  - Docket #5, case #500: Montana vs. K.A.R. Anderson and John Logan (re filing false reports on Columbus Bank; also includes material on Anderson and Logan Ranch), 1930-1931 (Box-folder 99 / 135)
  - Docket #5, case #503: Montana vs. Lionel C. Walsh and James F. Walsh (re Walsh Grain Company grain theft at Laurel), 1930-1931 (Box-folder 99 / 136)
  - Docket #5, case #533: Montana vs. Alva Askin (re appeal of Ekalaka manslaughter conviction; see also #464), 1931 (Box-folder 99 / 137)
  - Docket #5, case #534: Thomas H. Herrin vs. John E. Erickson (re state institutions bonds), 1931 (Box-folder 99 / 138)
  - Docket #5, case #535: Yale Oil Corporation of South Dakota (re appeal of gasoline tax case, see also #413), 1931 (Box-folder 99 / 139)
  - Docket #5, case #537: Montana vs. Hezekiah Benson (re attempt to maim livestock at Chinook), 1931 (Box-folder 99 / 140)
  - Docket #5, case #543: Standard Oil Company vs. Idaho Community Oil Company; Montana, intervenor (re taxes), 1931-1933 (Box-folder 99 / 141)
  - Docket #5, case #555: Laurel Oil and Refining Company bankruptcy (re delinquent taxes), 1931-1933 (Box-folder 99 / 142)
  - Docket #5, case #557: General American Tank Car Corporation vs. Sunburst Oil and Refining Company (re taxes due in receivership), 1930-1933 (Box-folder 99 / 143)
  - Docket #5, case #562: Montana vs. Alphonse Dachs (re involuntary manslaughter in car accident in Deer Lodge; also includes summary of cases prosecuted by county attorney's office 1931), 1931-1932 (Box-folder 99 / 144)
  - Docket #5, case #564: Montana vs. Fidelity and Deposit Company (re Chatterton and Son grain elevator, Billings), 1931-1936 (Box-folder 99 / 145)
  - Docket #5, case #565, 577: Montana vs. Earl Lund (re Great Western Bond and Mortgage Corporation embezzlement), 1932 (Box-folder 99 / 146)
  - Docket #5, case #568: George P. Porter, State Auditor vs. Investors' Syndicate (re proposed transfer of public domain to states), 1932-1936 (Box-folder 99 / 147)
  - Docket #5, case #569: Montana vs. Wyomont Producing and Refining Company (re license tax), 1931 (Box-folder 100 / 1)
  - Docket #5, case #572: Montana for the use of Henry Meyer vs. Federal Surety Company (re collection of bond), 1931-1935 (Box-folder 100 / 2)
  - Docket #5, case #574: Miller Insurance Agency vs. George P. Porter, State Auditor (re placing of state's insurance), 1932 (Box-folder 100 / 3)
  - Docket #5, case #578: Montana vs. Bud Phelps (re jurisdiction on Crow Reservation in grand larceny case), 1932 (Box-folder 100 / 4)
  - Docket #5, case #580: Montana vs. Bill McCracken (re grand larceny in Carter County), 1931-1933 (Box-folder 100 / 5)
  - Docket #5, case #582: Montana vs. Great Northern Railway (re collection of money spent fighting railroad-caused fire at Lupfer; includes list of fire fighters, description of fire, etc.), 1931-1933 (Box-folder 100 / 6)
  - Docket #5, case #583: Albert Nemitz vs. R.P. Reckards (to quiet title on land east of Great Falls), 1932-1933 (Box-folder 100 / 7)
  - Docket #5, case #585: Philip R. Barbour vs. State Board of Education (re Montana State University dormitory financing), 1931-1932 (Box-folder 100 / 8)
  - Docket #5, case #594: Judith Basin Irrigation District vs. Connor Malott and Eugene B. Favre (includes letters re Yellowstone Irrigation District at Forsyth), 1932-1933 (Box-folder 100 / 9)
  - Docket #6, case #6: Chicago, Milwaukee, and Saint Paul Railway vs. Fallon County (re taxes paid under protest), 1933 (Box-folder 100 / 10)
  - Docket #6, case #9: Montana vs. George Hoffman (re murder in Choteau), 1933 (Box-folder 100 / 11)
  - Docket #6, case #10: Montana ex rel. W.D. Tipton et al. vs. ...State Board of Examiners (re state funding bonds), 1933 (Box-folder 100 / 12)
  - Docket #6, case #11: Petition of Pietro Mario Amabile Notti, Italian Consul (re Frank Deorro Estate, Butte), 1930-1936 (Box-folder 100 / 13)
  - Docket #6, case #12: Montana vs. Jody Stokes (re murder and perjury in Hamilton), 1933 (Box-folder 100 / 14)
  - Docket #6, case #13: George Freeman vs. Abstractors Board of Examiners (re constitutionality of Abstractors Law; see also #121), 1932-1935 (Box-folder 100 / 15)
  - Docket #6, case #14: In the matter of Exchange Brokerage Company (re revocation of real estate license), 1933 (Box-folder 100 / 16)
  - Docket #6, case #15: H. Earl Clack Company vs. Public Service Commission (re distribution of gasoline), 1933 (Box-folder 100 / 17)
  - Docket #6, case #17: E.E. McMahon vs. State Board of Examiners (re fire insurance on state buildings), 1933 (Box-folder 100 / 18)
  - Docket #6, case #18: Montana vs. Wesley Jones (re robbery in Billings), 1933-1934 (Box-folder 100 / 19)
  - Docket #6, case #19: Thomas B. Rider vs. State Board of Land Commissioners (re grazing rental fees on state lands), 1933 (Box-folder 100 / 20)
  - Docket #6, case #20: Montana ex rel. Roundup Coal Company vs. Industrial Accident Board (re waiving statute of limitations in certain cases), 1933 (Box-folder 100 / 21)
  - Docket #6, case #21: A.J. Roberts, et al. vs. University Committee on Accountancy (re waiving of exam for certified public accountants), 1933 (Box-folder 100 / 22)
  - Docket #6, case #29: Montana vs. C.H. Drake and Ralph Smith (re arson in Conrad; also contains information re H.E. Freebury, George Moran, and arson in Belfry), 1932-1933 (Box-folder 100 / 23)
  - Docket #6, case #30: Montana vs. Montana Dakota Utilities Company (re natural gas tax), 1933 (Box-folder 100 / 24)
  - Docket #6, case #34: Montana ex rel. B.J. Kuhl vs. W.V. Kaiser, School District #55, Plevna (re school election), 1933 (Box-folder 100 / 25)
  - Docket #6, case #37: James E. Evans vs. Industrial Accident Board (re back injury), 1933 (Box-folder 100 / 26)
  - Docket #6, case #39: Montana vs. Joseph Henry Jennings (re second degree murder in Butte), 1933 (Box-folder 100 / 27)
  - Docket #6, case #40: Montana vs. J.B. Grimsley (re rustling in Phillips County), 1933-1934 (Box-folder 100 / 28)
  - Docket #6, case #41: John Farbo vs. School District #1, Toole County (re bonds), 1929, 1933 (Box-folder 100 / 29)
  - Docket #6, case #44: Montana vs. william Clarence Cates (re appeal of Missoula County murder conviction), 1934 (Box-folder 100 / 30)
  - Docket #6, case #46: Montana vs. James McAllister (re assault against J.P. Nelson at McAllister for attempted rape), 1933-1934 (Box-folder 100 / 31)
  - Docket #6, case #49: Montana vs. Harry Miller (re horse theft in Lewistown), 1934 (Box-folder 100 / 32)
  - Docket #6, case #50: Montana vs. L.R. Deams (re forgery in Harlowton), 1930-1934 (Box-folder 100 / 33)
  - Docket #6, case #56: Montana vs. A.G. Cathey (re second degree murder in Alzada), 1933 (Box-folder 100 / 34)
  - Docket #6, case #57: State Board of Dental Examiners vs. National Surety Company (re Dr. W.M. Smart's bond), 1932-1933 (Box-folder 100 / 35)
  - Docket #6, case #65: W.R. McDaniel vs. Eagle Coal Company and Industrial Accident Board (re injury), 1934-1935 (Box-folder 100 / 36)
  - Docket #6, case #66: Nelson Story Estate, Bozeman, 1933-1934 (Box-folder 100 / 37)
  - Docket #6, case #80: Superior Coal Company vs. Musselshell County (re taxing of coal reserves), 1934 (Box-folder 100 / 38)
  - Docket #6, case #82: G.S. Skekelton vs. Toole County (re election for bond issue), 1934 (Box-folder 100 / 39)
  - Docket #6, case #85: Montana ex rel. W.A. Blume vs. State Board of Education (re Eastern Montana Normal School bonds), 1934 (Box-folder 100 / 40)
  - Docket #6, case #93: Montana vs. Charles Wiles (re liquor in Havre), 1934 (Box-folder 100 / 41)
  - Docket #6, case #94: Montana vs. H.B. Lake (re theft by stockbroker), 1933-1934 (Box-folder 100 / 42)
  - Docket #6, case #95: Standard Oil Company of California vs. Idaho community Oil Company; Montana as intervenor (re taxation), 1930-1935 (Box-folder 100 / 43)
  - Docket #6, case #97: Industrial Accident Board vs.l Joseph D. Neville (re attorney's fees in injury suit), 1934 (Box-folder 100 / 44)
  - Docket #6, case #98: Sheldon Breeden vs. A.G. Shone and H.L. Maury (re Industrial Accident Board claim in Sheridan; disbarment), 1933-1934 (Box-folder 100 / 45)
  - Docket #6, case #99: Montana vs. Toney Neidamier (re selling narcotics in Great Falls), 1934 (Box-folder 100 / 46)
  - Docket #6, case #101: Montana ex rel. T.L. Hawkins vs. State Board of Examiners (re Tuberculosis Sanitarium at Galen), 1934 (Box-folder 100 / 47)
  - Docket #6, case #102: Montana vs. Elgin Daw (re assault in Ravalli County), 1934, 1936 (Box-folder 100 / 48)
  - Docket #6, case #105: Montana vs. Conrad Refining Company (re collection of oil royalties), 1934-1936 (Box-folder 100 / 49)
  - Docket #6, case #110: Montana vs. Leslie McCowan (re murder at Hall), 1933-1934 (Box-folder 100 / 50)
  - Docket #6, case #111: Montana vs. United States Guarantee Company (re re bond on highway project), 1934-1935 (Box-folder 100 / 51)
  - Docket #6, case #112: In the matter of Frank T. Hooks (re disbarment), 1934 (Box-folder 100 / 52)
  - Docket #6, case #115: Montana ex rel. Raymond T. Nagle, Attorney General vs. The Leader Company et al (re extension of corporate existence), 1931-1934 (Box-folder 100 / 53)
  - Docket #6, case #121: Montana ex rel. George Freeman vs. Abstractors Board of Examiners (re consistitutionality of Abstractors Law; see also #13), 1935 (Box-folder 100 / 54)
  - Docket #6, case #123: Montana vs Henry John Zorn, alias Henry J. Miller (re appeal of conviction in Miles City murder case), 1934-1935 (Box-folder 100 / 55)
  - Docket #6, case #124: Montana vs William Simanton (re rustling in Phillips County), 1935 (Box-folder 100 / 56)
  - Docket #6, case #129: Montana vs Frank Hogan (re robbery in Billings), 1935 (Box-folder 100 / 57)
  - Docket #6, case #132: Montana ex rel. J.R. Sparling vs. H.L. Hitsman, Daniels County Treasurer (re taxes by installments), 1935 (Box-folder 100 / 58)
  - Docket #6, case #134: V.W. Pomeroy vs. State Board of Equalization (re state income tax on federal employees), 1935 (Box-folder 100 / 59)
  - Docket #6, case #135: Montana ex rel. State Board of Education vs. Raymond T. Nagle, Attorney General (re employment of non-residents as teachers), 1935 (Box-folder 100 / 60)
  - Docket #6, case #136: Montana ex rel. City of Missoula vs. John J. Holmes, State Auditor (re insurance on city property), 1935 (Box-folder 100 / 61)
  - Docket #6, case #139: Industrial Accident Board vs. William Anderson (re insurance on phosphate mine at Garrison), 1934 (Box-folder 100 / 62)
  - Docket #6, case #140: John H. Garey vs. Industrial Accident Fund (re injury claim), 1934-1935 (Box-folder 100 / 63)
  - Docket #6, case #141: Montana vs. Sam Saari and John Saari (re arsons at Bearcreek, Columbus and Clancy), 1933 (Box-folder 100 / 64)
  - Docket #6, case #143: Montana vs. Pacific Gold Mining Company (re attachment), 1933 (Box-folder 100 / 65)
  - Docket #6, case #145: Aetna Casualty and Surety Company vs. A.R. Douglas et al. (re bankruptcy), 1933-1936 (Box-folder 100 / 66)
  - Docket #6, case #147: Northern Pacific Railway vs. Montana (re S.B. 27 requiring tail lights on locomotives), 1935 (Box-folder 100 / 67)
  - Docket #6, case #156: Mrs. George Tweedie vs. Industrial Accident Board (re death of husband in Red Lodge), 1934-1936 (Box-folder 100 / 68)
  - Docket #6, case #157-161: Montana ex rel. Raymond T. Nagle vs. Nick Pumnea (Capital Employment); William Tuohy (Rialto Bar); Harry Walker (New Deal Bar); F.E. Kessler (Tally's Gun Store); George Cooney (Mint Cigar Store) (re Helena gambling and liquor cases), 1935 (Box-folder 100 / 69)
  - Docket #6, case #162-170: Montana ex rel. Raymond T. Nagle vs. Clyde McRae (McRae's); Ted Traparich (Rocky Mountain Cafe); Peter Naughton (Crown Cigar Store); Peter Antonioli (M and M); James Red Gilmore (5-Mile Roadhouse); Joseph Parker (Walker's Cafe); Martin Kall (5-Mile Roadhouse); Carl Spillum (4 North Main); Julius Peters (Board of Trade) (re Butte gambling cases), 1935 (Box-folder 100 / 70)
  - Docket #6, case #171-176: Montana ex rel. Raymond T. Nagle vs. W.D. Mowre; Que Edwards (Stockmen's); John Gibbs (Silver Dollar); C.B. Strait (Senate Club); Joseph Simich (Brunswick Beer Parlor); Louis Sasick (Yellowstone Inn) (re Billings gambling cases), 1935 (Box-folder 100 / 71)
  - Docket #6, case #177-180: Montana ex rel. Raymond T. Nagle vs. William McFarland (Oxford Cigar Store); Charles Donovan (Donovan and Hickey Cigar Store); Fred Miles (Turf Soft Drink Parlor); Orin Dishman (New Mint Cigar Store) (re Missoula gambling cases), 1935 (Box-folder 100 / 72)
  - Docket #6, case #181: In the matter of Al Hanson (re disbarment), 1935-1936 (Box-folder 100 / 73)
  - Docket #6, case #182: Farmers State Bank vs. City of Conrad (re financing of new water system), 1935 (Box-folder 100 / 74)
  - Docket #6, case #187: Helen Johnson vs. City of Billings (re negligence in building of county road), 1935-1936 (Box-folder 100 / 75)
  - Docket #6, case #188: Montana vs. Peter Andre (re liquor in Granite County), 1934-1936 (Box-folder 100 / 76)
  - Docket #6, case #189: Montana vs. Sherman Clay Patton (re paternity case in Ekalaka), 1935 (Box-folder 100 / 77)
  - Docket #6, case #191: Charles Wilson Estate, Dillon, 1935-1936 (Box-folder 100 / 78)
  - Docket #6, case #197: Montana ex rel. E.A. Blenkner vs. Stillwater County (re Columbus State Bank failure), 1935-1937 (Box-folder 100 / 79)
  - Docket #6, case #201: Montana ex rel. Raymond T. Nagle vs. Merchants Credit Service Inc. (re illegal practice of law by collection agency in Great Falls), 1935-1936 (Box-folder 100 / 80)
  - Docket #6, case #206: Montana vs. Ed Clark et al. (re gambling in Ennis), 1936 (Box-folder 100 / 81)
  - Docket #6, case #211: L. Ray Carroll and J.B. Garrison vs. Sam Mitchell, Secretary of State (re state insurance law), 1935-1936 (Box-folder 100 / 82)
  - Docket #6, case #218, 223: Katherine Phillips vs. State Board of Equalization (re liquor in Helena), 1933-1936 (Box-folder 100 / 83)
  - Docket #6, case #235, 276: Montana vs. A.J. Lee (re condemnation of land for School of Mines, Butte), 1934-1936 (Box-folder 100 / 84)
  - Docket #6, case #236: Montana vs. I.W. Stephens (re selling asperin without license in Billings), 1936 (Box-folder 100 / 85)
  - Docket #6, case #237: Investors Security Company vs. Charles Walton, Wheatland County Treasurer (re taxes paid under protest), 1936-1942 (Box-folder 100 / 86)
  - Docket #6, case #240: Toole County Irrigation District vs. State Board of Land Commissioners (re taxation of state land within district), 1935-1936 (Box-folder 100 / 87)
  - Docket #6, case #244: Montana vs. Roy Peterson (re rape in Great Falls), 1936 (Box-folder 100 / 88)
  - Docket #6, case #245: Montana ex rel. F.W. Wilson vs. State Board of Education (re Montana State University journalism building), 1937 (Box-folder 100 / 89)
  - Docket #6, case #255: Edward W. Thomas vs. State Board of Examiners (re state insurance law), 1936 (Box-folder 100 / 90)
  - Docket #6, case #256: Montana ex rel. Raymond T. Nagle vs. John F. McGough (re gambling in Boulder), 1934-1935 (Box-folder 100 / 91)
  - Docket #6, case #257: Montana vs. Thomas Carey (re "lewd act with minor" (homosexual) by state official), 1935 (Box-folder 100 / 92)